difficult?
難しい?
think.
考 えて
difficult.
難しい
Can I come in?
入れていい?
Shall I put it in?
入れようか
hey.
ね
What about sesame seeds?
ごまは?
It's on.
ついてるよ
It's not on.
ついてないよ
Did you notice?
気づいた?
Today, I want to leave it like this.
今日さ、 このまま入れたい
It's dangerous.
危険だよ
Is it dangerous?
危険だ?
But, you can just take it outside, right?
でもさ、 外に出せばいいでしょ?
I think it's okay as long as you don't let it go inside.
中に出さなかったら大丈夫だと思うよ
Got it.
分かった
Just for a moment.
一瞬だけ
Let me put it in just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ入れさせて
Every moment.
一瞬一瞬
It's just a moment, right?
一瞬でしょ?
It's only a moment.
まだ一瞬だよ
Put it on already.
もうつけて
That's fine.
いいじゃん
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ?
Even four years ago.
4つ前だって
difficult.
難しい
It was AV.
AVでしたさ
I've never seen it.
見たことないんだけど
Did you see it?
見た?
I'll go.
行くよ
No.
ダメ